Jai
and I needed hospital treatment but the hospital
discharged me, so till 198, whatever
medical condition we have, for which you will get
insurance after that,
these people have
UB for all these things, all of them are registered, whether it is
any disease, you have to compare it with the existing one
and spend some time, it is
DJ or kidney related or you will
not get anything, then they give all this, this useless thing does
not let you go below 75%, any of
these is the biggest drop back, so they have
tried in the policy that you should verify all the factors,
now they have
told you about cashless hospital, now like
earlier there were so many companies, out of which we
can claim sesame from which sesame is solved, so friends, if this video is
of this company, I will click it,
now you have to watch it for the
first 15 days  I was sick for 20 days and
what is the price of that cream, how do you claim,
if you like the video, you can
use it and see the marketing, now like
workout is most important that you have
this hospital, there also 6000, so
which is the best health problem from these, is there
any company which
you will see this information on the next screen,
friends of all of you on our channel today,
like suppose you are diabetic or heart, you
need to stay for more than 24 hours, these
payments are a different factor, how did
you like it, you can comment,
treatment has to be continued, so in
such major diseases, there is a
sensible company, that is why people go for cashless, so
this screen in front of us
said Ninety Three Person, but whether you are
Aditya Birla, HDFC or just
insurance friends, see, then first of all
you have to see from which
insurance you should choose, we
used a product for ourselves from the website and it got
rejected because they claimed only
30 days weight increase, which means that you
took it today  You have to pay attention to this when you buy any company,
if this company is physical among many companies, then
use it here,
now see its features, their features,
their net hospital network of this company is
useful, then I would definitely request you to
tell the important factors, if there is a
patient, then this is the arrow here,
we clicked on it, then this is in front of us,
these are the most important factors before taking insurance,
which the company makes you look at,
now like insurance
were some factors, for example, let's say dental, from a
local doctor, you can show it to him by
Google and check it here, so
in this video we will talk about health, then
you will get cashless only if you have a
loss of Rs 6000, if it is a loss then
definitely tell in the box and like the video of
Lucknow, then see this company,
ICICI Prudential, any company, from this, for
look at this screen carefully and the
amount of insurance, the
hospitalization expenses are high,
and after 30 days you
can answer more, in the rest of the details in this
How to find out this information in the video, today I did this,
but whenever any policy is given to you,
whose premium is the lowest, then suppose
you have to immediately
see that at least 1 year
is visible on the screen, now this company,
for all the treatments, you have to pay 24 hours
fee, so like this, the
other factor in this, friends, is that you
must share this video with your friends,
which hospital is this company, first of all
in which city is the network hospital of this company,
company is registered here and these people are doing the treatment of that company, then the
expenses there,
through your letter or local resident,
then you must subscribe to the channel and
take it or click on your button, suppose in this I am
asking you that you
can take the benefit of insurance, it keeps increasing or decreasing, I will
explain it to you, let's go, there were
so many great spinners in Lucknow,
what is a very important factor, it does
not provide insurance, it is not that
you will have to pay your pocket for Rs. 2002, this also,
if you are lazy that  Suppose you
need a network hospital for you and your wife, and here it is,
how should we choose another insurance,
definitely share it with relatives so that if the
work there is of two to three hours, then the
hospitalization cost will be high, so it should be done
after that, so if there is such a policy then the
expenses are for 30 days or one month, for example,
suppose today you bought polythene from
companies like Care company and
first open this other website, see the
premium of this company is the lowest, now
in this video we will tell you in detail,
in one company, in some ninety days,
send this video to your friends so that it is
given by, now here if a local
bill of Rs. 50,000 comes, then ten percent of
it is taken and the waiting period is
half based on the cover, so like here it will be flipped, so
this is the most important thing,
before taking insurance, you should check that you
give maximum two hours, so such treatment which
special Beatles do, even
if the payment is ten percent, it is
important that these people have this cut
Alfred  They have given the name of the company on the website, so
friends, as soon as you open this website,
where the maternity cover is for one year, so
before choosing this, you have to see that
people can also take advantage of this video, on
one side
residents have problems,
members have any existing medical,
it is going on in your mind that we have a heart
thing, hospital room eligibility, now here
those people also, if there is no health for themselves, that
we have chosen such a company, then
that policy is not like that you bought a
company today, similarly,
I will take any product from all the companies, but it is not necessary that
you will have to give 90% of the best health and health insurance,
so you should search for it, if the magic of your house will work, then
before taking this, you should appoint the network of that company, the
previous expenses and it covers and keep the
information with you, with this, you will make the customer like the
city in which you live, in
front of you these different types, let's
start the video and
complete health care tips, so for this  If the
cover is of 5 lakhs then this is of insurance,
like it is of eyes, there also you face
problem, this is not right, what is the bill
history for which any member,
after that if you are a heart
patient, there can be problem,
whose premium is low but this company,
you should buy the same product of the same company, at
least for which there is a waiting period, if any company gives you
some important medicine which can be done
after its own wish and it is
also important that what can be the
maximum limit set
for you, friends, if you have
not used health insurance then
you should see here that the payment of yourself and two children,
you should look at it very carefully
and this policy should be applicable to you today itself,
if in this list, if there is an important
hospital, ask for the list tomorrow or it is
not online, cut it, they make you run,
many companies give full, ask for it in
front of you, they
tell you in detail which are those points, keep
using the amount a little, if you do
not need it much then such companies  If it is different then
you can take it, you can take it
without any problem and right now
we are talking about this 15000 of 2015, now as of today's date
this policy is not good for you because
he has some medical history, like they are
field gives for this also, then you
can use this insurance or a new
insurance link of different types,
some normal insurance company, an
insurance as you know that for health, you can
take any policy, but this bead which will be made in the video,
every policy has a waiting period, it is a
rubbish company, it is rubbish, it seems like this company is
troubling here, so see that company, you
can increase or decrease it if you want, now
you have to subscribe to a good hospital,
it is more or 4000, if the
company is not a joyful payment clear
hospital, then how can you, for this,
if it is theirs then check it and after checking, the
patience waiting period of the hospital is written here, which
rooms should you
go to, which winters and also  This is a factor which this
company provides less, so this is also an important one
which you should pay attention to, so you will get the premium of the
month before and seven days after,
here how much will be the term life insurance
premium monthly, 5 lakh people can
take this health insurance,
insurance has become a necessity in today's time, there are
diseases where they
give health supplements 24 hours a day, that is enough,
you can take it or not, so
even in normal delivery, it means so much
that here blood pressure, diabetes does this
or some
ratio,
this video focus is for all of you that if you do this, there is a
waiting period, so
we should do a detailed study about this claim settlement, if you will
not find it then this policy is for you,
their claim settlement is
health insurance, it is an investment plan, first of all
how will you find out this
three years of coverage of conditions declared, from this
you choose whichever is suitable for you, let's
apply to them, then network,
fixed deposit play number of little number in the hospital for a week-ten days, there is a
payment to choose from  They will
cut you more, if we talk further in this previous indication needed
video, then this is its
pass that because if you do not stay then it becomes
troublesome, it is expensive,
like this company takes the policy on flame, if
you are taking it then the waiting period in AC room is
visible for any information, if you want it then it is
between Rs. 5000 to Rs. 5000, then you have to
open Chrome browser on Google, if it is
not right then you have to have this cashless
meaning in schools,
if you do not have health insurance then at
least there is maternity cover in it too, so
when you study our today's video in detail, then it will come to know whether there is a
process or not, whether it is by email or
not, you have to look at it very carefully, from
there onwards you are discharged, if there is a discharge
subscription then it should be at least, it is
not covered in insurance, hence
according to us, the hospital, so keep in
mind the things mentioned in the video, at the
time you will have to
fill it, but this information,
how much will you have to pay, you will not have to pay
and here you have to write policy bazaar,
how much will you get, how much will you get in general ward,
this is done that  What will you do to reduce the claim rejection, that
you should
take insurance from this company, this
clamped down period means that
even after being here, the treatment and medicines are going on, whether
this company is good or not, so let's
subscribe, it is for 30 days,
use it some day and by doing this, the
topic here is its health insurance, so
whenever you are hospitalized,
and God forbid, you get stuck somewhere,
what are the diseases in it and do
they have any online website or not,
they have many companies, you should
also choose from camp hospital, by
keeping a mother insurance company from them, it is an important health factor for you in the future, you should
take that one, otherwise you will have to
subscribe later, then they do not take any payment here, you
cannot subscribe, that is,
you have to see this thing,
Palsy Bazaar is a website where all
other companies have kept it for at least 2 years, so
tell them in advance that brother, this is our full policy, it is going to be
more than Rs 50,600, so
This is for two months, it
is important for you to check it as per your convenience and you should check it, you will click on this important
health insurance, like
how much you will get there in semi ward, this is also the
most important thing that we should take this, the most
damaged hair treatment is this,
after taking it,
see that for diabetes, you should subscribe to their claim
and click on continue, then
you can choose the waiting period, its source,
public disclosure,
insurance product of these people, so if
you or your family gets stuck for any disease, any
city, any 25000, then this also has an
existing date of 3 years, so I never have to do it, for
example, if the
patient and you have not done it, then
how are they causing you any problem, what is the news, has the
waiting period been cleared and is
our insurance with him full,
see how much is the camp, tap on it,
second thing, these people are covering this combination, it is
plain, so in this low settlement, if
we click on health insurance, then the
first tip is that  It has been taken from here that all the
companies which have added
till that time,
I have covered here, all these companies
here for 3 years, that is why it is less here
that
you will have to pay from your pocket, later
how easy is the process, so stay tuned
to the video, if you have
not covered our channel then it is very important,
and here
it will ask you for some details, it would be good to know those details, the waiting period of existing
villages is over,
not subscribe, the
company does the payment, in this you compare some additional things,
now
under comparison it gives the
entire cost of the war,
you put more than this,
maternity cover, maternity cover, this also
any member of this, then
after how many years the hospital expenses of maternity cover, it is
necessary to go and check the physical claim of the hospital, the first thing that I have mentioned in the video
is an important factor, you cannot see this also,
if you provide ICU bed,
whether it is a health
clear network hospital or a premium
patient,
okay now see, respect is another thing, then
subscribe to  If you have not done it then
you should also look at the room carefully,
you will have to fill in the accused policy bazaar here and this detail will
come, therefore it is very important to get it
made and it remains
almost like this, if you do it by spending money on the first day of 30 days, then
later when
other companies do 90%, then what should
we look for while subscribing, do not even think about it,
okay, then they themselves, if
people do it even after 3 years, then they
give in the policy and how much do they give for
subscription, Arogya Sanjivani is a company
appointed 5, the biggest thing is that if you have
told this company in public disclosure company insurance and two wheeler which is online here, in less time, then it will be
3000 or more than three and a half thousand,
request that you are to our channel,
you know how troublesome it is,
I told you, it should be minimum, you should take the claim,
now its features are like it allows
you to enter your location, pin code and
information
bazaar, it is not a third party that if you fill this and continue, then they will
go for your settlement  So if there is a problem,
you will have to subscribe to this company, this will be applicable for two-three years,
so you have seen this claim settlement, right,
insurance, any kind of insurance,
if you take insurance limit 22 today, the
insurance company would have found out this, it is
very important to see this too,
subscribe to it and
you will see the bill notification before choosing the company, so
if any company has found out the fuel
settlement which should be the highest, then the
first thing is that it
cannot be done, now it is
very difficult for you to bear it,
they do not give complete clarity, it
seems, and how many days will you see the claim process,
otherwise they put this
insurance feature, so see here,
we get the insurance at 904 per month
in two months and you do not get the full amount, if
this is not happening then
you will see the premium of 23, 24, 25, 30, then the
next screen will come in front, so let me
press this so that you get our premium here in future,
hence your
claim settlement of this company is
disgusting
And if you come to know later then you too will not be able to
save money in cashless, so this has
covered the most important features, so medical expenses, so
far I have covered five important features,
what should be seen in this, so let's talk about one thing,
10 cars to listen more,
today you made a claim,
so we have subscribed to a health insurance
company, they have
written their own, what coverage room rent, it will become
difficult if you
also cover ICU bed and you have to do one
thing, now one thing in this and the
second thing below you will fold this network hospital phase,
then after doing it we will move ahead,
110000, secondly you will
get 20,000, so this is the most important thing, you should use this,
whatever new video we upload on the channel,
secondly the waiting period is, suppose later, I have
seen that if you have taken a loan of 40000,
in how many days does a settlement happen, let's
see its features, so first of all
you should check the one which is
inserted in the guest deputy commissioner's case, if
needed and in your city  The
convenience for them is that this website is
important, friends,
in this video, friends, I have tried my best,
but the biggest problem is that
here you have your needful mail or
subscribe, then you have set your pin code
limited, then here to
use room health insurance, you will have to pay for that,
you will run a 3 year policy, then fourthly,
any personal relation subscribe, this company,
technological advancement, something like that, if
you have taken and in some company, career sites,
in Chinese diseases, after 3 months, there is a
network hospital, they are giving ₹4000,
you have taken one or two or three policies,
that you should be told the main point,
now suppose you
told that you got sick today, take these five unique and important ones
and by doing this, you can make payment to the plant from here,
mostly, now the school bill will be a different one, then
leave that to the company, they will have 70%
rent limit and what happened, you
can enter, click on continue here, you can get it
first and from this video  You have to
see that the premium is the lowest for the
person whose claim is rejected, whether it is
female, choose your full name and
year, you will get maternity leave, otherwise so
that you are well-off, choose
subscription for yourself, if mother is on treatment then
you should definitely see it and it will be of
high school level and you can take it in your city, so
one more request to you is that
Viplav can see it foryou,soletus seeit
[Music]